[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a branch of science that deals with the design and development processes of algorithms that enable computers to learn based on data types?",
    "answer1": "Machine Learning",
    "answer2": "Artificial intelligence",
    "answer3": "Image processing",
    "answer4": "Neural Network",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"

  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the term machine learning coined?",
    "answer1": "1955",
    "answer2": "1959",
    "answer3": "1958",
    "answer4": "1960",
    "rightAnswer": "answer2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the American person who coined the term machine learning, pioneer in computer games and artificial intelligence, and also an IBMer?",
    "answer1": "Alan Turing",
    "answer2": "Steve Jobs",
    "answer3": "Artur Samuel",
    "answer4": "Bill Gates",
    "rightAnswer": "answer3"
  },
  {
"question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms produces a function that maps inputs to target outputs?",
    "answer1": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer2": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer3": "non-reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "supervised learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer4"
  },
  {
   "question": "What are the two main goals of modern machine learning today?",
    "answer1": "Classification and prediction",
    "answer2": "Classification and accumulation",
    "answer3": "Estimating and accumulating",
    "answer4": "Data sampling and classification",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
  {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms models an input set?",
    "answer1": "supervised learning",
    "answer2": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer3": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "learning to learn",
    "rightAnswer": "answer2"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms is concerned with what actions it must take in order to achieve the highest amount of reward in an environment?",
    "answer1": "supervised learning",
    "answer2": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer3": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "semi-supervised learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer3"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms considers labeled and unlabeled examples together to create appropriate functions or classifiers?",
    "answer1": "supervised learning",
    "answer2": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer3": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "semi-supervised learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer4"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms provides learning by making use of previous experiences?",
    "answer1": "learning to learn",
    "answer2": "supervised learning",
    "answer3": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer4": "reinforcement learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the sample set used in one iteration of model training?",
    "answer1": "Batch",
    "answer2": "Batch size",
    "answer3": "Baseline",
    "answer4": "Bucketing",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following terms is a statistical analysis technique used to extract a representative subset from a data?",
    "answer1": "Data sampling",
    "answer2": "Data set",
    "answer3": "Bucketing",
    "answer4": "Classification",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following terms refers to an intersection or offset from a source?",
    "answer1": "Bias",
    "answer2": "Classification",
    "answer3": "Bucketing",
    "answer4": "Batch",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following is not one of the steps in building a machine learning model?",
    "answer1": "Deterioration of the model",
    "answer2": "Designing the model",
    "answer3": "Testing the model",
    "answer4": "Implementation of the model",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a branch of science that deals with the design and development processes of algorithms that enable computers to learn based on data types?",
    "answer1": "Machine Learning",
    "answer2": "Artificial intelligence",
    "answer3": "Image processing",
    "answer4": "Neural Network",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"

  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the term machine learning coined?",
    "answer1": "1955",
    "answer2": "1959",
    "answer3": "1958",
    "answer4": "1960",
    "rightAnswer": "answer2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the American person who coined the term machine learning, pioneer in computer games and artificial intelligence, and also an IBMer?",
    "answer1": "Alan Turing",
    "answer2": "Steve Jobs",
    "answer3": "Artur Samuel",
    "answer4": "Bill Gates",
    "rightAnswer": "answer3"
  },
  {
"question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms produces a function that maps inputs to target outputs?",
    "answer1": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer2": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer3": "non-reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "supervised learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer4"
  },
  {
   "question": "What are the two main goals of modern machine learning today?",
    "answer1": "Classification and prediction",
    "answer2": "Classification and accumulation",
    "answer3": "Estimating and accumulating",
    "answer4": "Data sampling and classification",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
  {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms models an input set?",
    "answer1": "supervised learning",
    "answer2": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer3": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "learning to learn",
    "rightAnswer": "answer2"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms is concerned with what actions it must take in order to achieve the highest amount of reward in an environment?",
    "answer1": "supervised learning",
    "answer2": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer3": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "semi-supervised learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer3"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms considers labeled and unlabeled examples together to create appropriate functions or classifiers?",
    "answer1": "supervised learning",
    "answer2": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer3": "reinforcement learning",
    "answer4": "semi-supervised learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer4"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the machine learning algorithms provides learning by making use of previous experiences?",
    "answer1": "learning to learn",
    "answer2": "supervised learning",
    "answer3": "unsupervised learning",
    "answer4": "reinforcement learning",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the sample set used in one iteration of model training?",
    "answer1": "Batch",
    "answer2": "Batch size",
    "answer3": "Baseline",
    "answer4": "Bucketing",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following terms is a statistical analysis technique used to extract a representative subset from a data?",
    "answer1": "Data sampling",
    "answer2": "Data set",
    "answer3": "Bucketing",
    "answer4": "Classification",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following terms refers to an intersection or offset from a source?",
    "answer1": "Bias",
    "answer2": "Classification",
    "answer3": "Bucketing",
    "answer4": "Batch",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  },
    {
  "question": "Which of the following is not one of the steps in building a machine learning model?",
    "answer1": "Deterioration of the model",
    "answer2": "Designing the model",
    "answer3": "Testing the model",
    "answer4": "Implementation of the model",
    "rightAnswer": "answer1"
  }
  
  
]
